[
  {"questionText": "Which of the following is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?", "options": ["VAR", "LET", "CONST", "ALL OF THE ABOVE"], "correctIndex": 3, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "Which symbol is used for comments in JavaScript (single-line)?", "options": ["//", "<!--", "#", "**"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "Which data type is NOT a primitive type in JavaScript?", "options": ["STRING", "BOOLEAN", "OBJECT", "NUMBER"], "correctIndex": 2, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "Which method is used to convert a string to lowercase?", "options": ["toLowerCase()", "lowerCase()", "changeCaseLower()", "strLower()"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "JavaScript can be used for both frontend and backend development.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "JavaScript is case-sensitive.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "Functions can be stored in variables in JavaScript.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "Which of these is a JavaScript framework?", "options": ["React", "Laravel", "Django", "Flask"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "Which operator is used for strict equality?", "options": ["==", "===", "=", "All of the above"], "correctIndex": 1, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "Strings in JavaScript are mutable", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 2, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "What is typeof null in JavaScript?", "options": ["Null", "Undifiend", "Object", "Number"], "correctIndex": 2, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "var and let have the same scope rules.", "options":  ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "The === operator ignores type when comparing values", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "How do you write an array in JavaScript?", "options": ["var colors = 'red', 'blue', 'green';", "var colors = ['red', 'blue', 'green'];", "var colors = {red, blue, green};", "var colors = (red, blue, green);"], "correctIndex": 1, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "Arrays in JavaScript can store values of different types.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "JSON_VALUE() can extract a scalar value from a JSON string.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "Which of these is NOT a JavaScript data type?", "options": ["Number", "String", "Float", "Boolean"], "correctIndex": 2, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "JavaScript can run in any web browser without additional software.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true},
  {"questionText": "What is the correct way to call a function named start()?", "options": ["call start", "start;", "start()", "call.start"], "correctIndex": 2, "isTrueFalse": false},
  {"questionText": "alert() displays a message in the browser.", "options": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "isTrueFalse": true}
]